* |
* |
* |
* |

### Toll-FREE: [1-866-873-6574](tel:1-866-873-6574)

### Toll-FREE: [1-866-873-6574](tel:1-866-873-6574)

Privacy Policy
==============

### Our commitment to you.

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### The information we collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on any and all Acorn Stairlifts website(s). On some pages you can request further information, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

* Name,
* Address
* Email address,
* Telephone number.

### The way we use information

We do not share any information provided by you with outside parties, without your prior approval.  
We use the information you provide about you or someone else when requesting information only as contact details to provide you with the information you requested, or to transfer the materials you have requested.  
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.  
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website. For example, we may compile data showing the number of visitors to areas of the site(s), or the number who completed a form, but nothing is used that could identify those individuals.  
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

### Our commitment to data security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Our commitment to children's privacy

WProtecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

### How you can access or correct your information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by sending us an email at privacy@acornstairlifts.com and requesting it.  
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.  
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

### How to contact us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at privacy@acornstairlifts.com

* Acorn Stairlifts Inc.
* 7001 Lake Ellenor Drive
* Orlando
* Florida 32809
* USA

##### Toll-FREE: [1-866-873-6574](tel:1-866-873-6574)

##### Our Stairlifts

##### Check out the Acorn Stairlifts YouTube channel for informative videos and news.

**Keep up to date with Acorn Stairlifts on social media!**

##### Keep up to date with Acorn Stairlifts on social media!

All Rights Reserved  
© 2024 Acorn Stairlifts Inc.

All Rights Reserved  
© 2024 Acorn Stairlifts Inc.
